vrfocus.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy – VRFocus

**This privacy policy governs the collection, storage, use of personal information collected by **VRFocus.com**. It provides details about the personal information that we collect from you, how we use your personal information, your rights regarding the personal information that we hold about you. Please read this privacy policy carefully – by using our services, you confirm that you have read, understood, agree to this privacy policy in its entirety.**

Joe Bachle-Morris, Chief Operating Officer, **WAM Group Ltd.** : joe.bachle-morris@admix.in

WAM Group Ltd. (together with its subsidiaries, “vrfocus.com” or “we”) has adopted a set of Privacy Principles applicable to all UK-based companies. **VRFocus.com** has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use, and share personally identifiable information (information that can be used to identify you, such as your full name, email address, mailing address, or telephone number) (“PII”) we obtain from and about individuals located in the UK both online and offline.

**VRFocus.com** is a general audience website, and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time we may revise this Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our information collection and use practices, the features of **VRFocus.com** , or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If we materially change our practices regarding use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

#### Collection of PII by VRFocus

**General**. **VRFocus.com** collects PII in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in certain activities including (i) registration for certain online services and tools such as downloads, message boards, chat rooms or other community services; (ii) registration for special communications, such as email updates and newsletters; (iii) subscription registration; (iv) purchase products or services from or through **VRFocus.com** ; (v) user surveys; (vi) events, sweepstakes, contests or promotions; and (vii) registration for online multi- or single-player gaming. We may obtain PII from third parties that we consider to be reputable.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of **VRFocus.com** , such as the member home pages and forum, your information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing PII, such as full name, home address, or phone number.

**Cookies**. Cookies are small bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit **VRFocus.com**. We may use cookies to recognize users who have already registered, allowing those users to speed up their future activities.

Third party advertisements displayed on **VRFocus.com** may also contain cookies set by internet advertising companies or advertisers. **VRFocus.com** does not control these cookies. You should check the privacy policy of the internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

You can set your computer to alert you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on **VRFocus.com**.

#### VRFocus’ Use of PII

WAM Group Ltd. will use your PII in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. **VRFocus.com** may use PII in aggregate, anonymous form for research purposes.

We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration, for customer service purposes or for any other business reason related to your use **VRFocus.com**.

All of **VRFocus.com** ’s policy is delivered in accordance with UK law. All data collected by **VRFocus.com** is held within the UK and not shared with any external company or entity without consent. The collection of PII and the responsibilities of the authorities collecting such data may differ in countries not governed by UK law, for which WAM Group Ltd. cannot be accountable for.

#### How long does VRFocus Keep your PII?

Cookie data is typically stored for a period of 56 months, unless otherwise determined by your browser. Other information is not stored without direct user consent; i.e. opting into a mailing list.

#### What are your rights in relation to the information VRFocus.com collects?

You have the following rights:

• to ask us to provide you with copies of personal information that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law;

• to ask us to update or correct any out of date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you (in accordance with applicable data protection legislation);

• to request that we send you (or another data controller) your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format (in accordance with applicable data protection laws); and

• the right to opt-out of any marketing communications that we (or any third party to whom we have disclosed your personal information with your consent) may send you.

If you want to exercise any of these rights, please write to us (either by post or e-mail) at the address specified below.

If you object to our processing of your personal information for certain purposes or you want us to stop using or to delete your personal information, you can contact us and tell us why. In certain circumstances we may not be able to stop using your personal information but, if that is the case, we’ll let you know and tell you why.

If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated. Please contact us at joe.bachle-morris@admix.in.

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal information accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office <https://ico.org.uk/> or seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been breached.
